// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is not an OOPS concept?",
    answer: "Exception",
    options: [
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Exception",
      "Abstraction"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which among the following feature is not in the general definition of OOPS?",
    answer: "Duplicate or Redundant Data",
    options: [
      "Modularity",
      "Efficient Code",
      "Code reusability",
      "Duplicate or Redundant Data"
    
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which feature of OOPS described the reusability of code?",
    answer: "Inheritance",
    options: [
      "Abstraction",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Inheritance"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which feature of OOPS derives the class from another class?",
    answer: "Inheritance",
    options: [
      "Inheritance",
      "Data hiding",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "A single program of OOPS contains ___ classes?",
    answer: "Any number",
    options: [
      "Only 1",
      "Only 999",
      "Only 100",
      "Any number"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which two features of object-oriented programming are the same?",
    answer: "Encapsulation and Abstraction",
    options: [
      "Abstraction and Polymorphism features are the same",
      "Inheritance and Encapsulation features are the same",
      "Encapsulation and Polymorphism features are the same",
      "Encapsulation and Abstraction"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which header file is required by the C++ programming language to use the OOPS concept?",
    answer: "We can easily use the OOPS concepts in c++ programs without using any header file.",
    options: [
      "stdio.h",
      "iostream.h",
      "stdlib.h",
      "We can easily use the OOPS concepts in c++ programs without using any header file."
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following definition is incorrect for polymorphism?",
    answer: "It always increases the overhead of function definition",
    options: [
      "Polymorphism helps in redefining the same functionality",
      "Polymorphism concept is the feature of object-oriented programming (OOP)",
      "It always increases the overhead of function definition",
      "Ease in the readability of the program"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following OOP concept is not true for the C++ programming language?",
    answer: "C++ Program must contain at least one class",
    options: [
      "A class must have member functions",
      "C++ Program can be easily written without the use of classes",
      "At least one instance should be declared within the C++ program",
      "C++ Program must contain at least one class"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following OOP concept binds the code and data together and keeps them secure from the outside world?",
    answer: "Encapsulation",
    options: [
      "Polymorphism",
      "Inheritance",
      "Abstraction",
      "Encapsulation"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];